ILGWU Education Department Publications 5780/166 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Union Service. How To Build Your Union., 1947-1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: How To Build Your Union., Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Education Department. Training for Union Service. Second copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Union Service. Special Problems in Organization., 1946-1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Special Problems in Organization., Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Education Department. Training for Union Service.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Union Service. Who Sets the Styles?, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Who Sets the Styles?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Union Service. Womens Garment Industry., 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Womens Garment Industry., Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Trade Union Policies and Tactics: An Outline, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Educational Series no.2. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Trade Union Policies and Tactics: An Outline, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
    By David J. Saposs. Educational Series no.2. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. The Union of the Womens Garment Workers., 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Filmstrip no.3.
  - Item 1: The Union of the Womens Garment Workers., Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
    By Education Department. Filmstrip no.3. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. The Union Way., 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  A Guide Toward Union Principles and Practice. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: The Union Way., Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    By Education Department. A Guide Toward Union Principles and Practice. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. The Uprising of the Twenty Thousand., 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  The General Strike of the Waistmakers of 1909. By Daniel Nelson. November 1959.
  - Item 1: The Uprising of the Twenty Thousand: The General Strike of the Waistmakers of 1909., Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    By Daniel Nelson. Summary of a Discussion. November 19, 1959. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Use Filmstrips., 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Use Filmstrips., Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. What They Say About "With These Hands", Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: What They Say About "With These Hands", Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Who Makes Public Opinion?, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Part 1. March 1949.
  - Item 1: Who Makes Public Opinion? Part 1., Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    By Fannia Cohn. March 26, 1949. second copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Workers Education in the ILGWU, 1937-1940, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Excerpts from the General Executive Board Report. 1940. 4 copies.
  - Item 1: Workers Education in the ILGWU, 1937-1940, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    By Education Department. Excerpts from the General Executive Board Report. 1940. 4 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Yak-Yak., 1954-1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  no.8-11 (1954); no.12-+13,15 (1955); no.18 (1956). 2 copies each of no. 15 and 18.
  - Item 1: Yak-Yak., Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    By Education Department. no.8-11 (1954). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Yak-Yak., Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    By Education Department. no.12-13,15 (1955). 2 copies of no. 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Yak-Yak., Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    By Education Department. no.18 (1956). 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. You and the World., 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  October 1948.
  - Item 1: You and the World: Learn, Play, Act., Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    By Education Department. October 1948. Second copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. You and Your Union., 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: You and Your Union., Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
- I.L.G.W.U. Handcraft Studios. Crafty News Notes., 1954-1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  v.1:no.1 (1954:Sep.); v.2:no.1 (1955:June); v.2:no.2 (1955:Sep.)
  - Item 1: Crafty News Notes., Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
    By Handcraft Studios. v.1:no.1 (1954:Sep.); v.2:no.1 (1955:June); v.2:no.2 (1955:Sep.). Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1937; Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
    By Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
    By Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
  1 complete copy and 1 incomplete copy.
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
    By Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. 1 complete copy and 1 incomplete copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
    By Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council. Report of Activities., 1970-1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Report of Activities., Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
- I.L.G.W.U. Local 22. Club 22 Chat., 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
  v.1:no.4 (1955:Jan.)
  - Item 1: Club 22 Chat., Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
    By Local 22. v.1:no.4 (1955:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Education Program: Local 22, Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
    By Local 22. Flyer. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Los Angeles Dress and Sportswear Joint Board, Los Angeles Cloak Joint Board. Organization Department. Guide for House Call Committees., Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Guide for House Call Committees., Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    By Los Angeles Dress and Sportswear Joint Board, Los Angeles Cloak Joint Board. Organization Department. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Los Angeles Education Department. Singing Union., Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Singing Union., Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
    By Los Angeles Education Department. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Meet the I.L.G.W.U., 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
  April 1941.
  - Item 1: Meet the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
    April 1941.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. The Pennsylvania Organizer., 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
  no.2 (1955:Oct.)
  - Item 1: The Pennsylvania Organizer., Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
    no.2 (1955:Oct.). Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Pleased to Meet You., Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
  3 identical copies, plus one slightly different
  - Item 1: Pleased to Meet You., Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Flyers. 3 identical copies, plus one slightly different. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. The Position of the I.L.G.W.U. in relation to the CIO and AFL. 1934-1938., Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: The Position of the I.L.G.W.U. in relation to the CIO and AFL. 1934-1938., Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
    December, 1938. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board of the I.L.G.W.U., 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
  November, 1971.
  - Item 1: Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
    November, 1971. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board of the I.L.G.W.U., 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
  February, 1977.
  - Item 1: Report to the Education Committee of the General Executive Board of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
    February, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Memo: For Staff Only, Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
    v.2:no.1 (1977:Jan.). Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Rivera Murals., 1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Rivera Murals., Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Songs., Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Songs., Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
- I.L.G.W.U. Southwest Region. Educational Activities Report. 1954-1956., Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Educational Activities Report. 1954-1956., Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
    By Education Department Southwest Region.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Southwest Region. What the St. Louis ILGWU Social Service Dept. Does., 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: What the St. Louis ILGWU Social Service Dept. Does., Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
- I.L.G.W.U. Southwest Region. Why Workers Should Be Affiliated With a Union., 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Why Workers Should Be Affiliated With a Union., Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    By Education Department Southwest Region.. April 2, 1953. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. This is the Union of the Garment Workers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: This is the Union of the Garment Workers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
    2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Todo Trabajador Deberia Ganar Por Lo Menos $1.25 la Hora, 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Todo Trabajador Deberia Ganar Por Lo Menos $1.25 la Hora, Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
    Item is in Spanish.
- I.L.G.W.U. Training Institute. Preparing for a Career in Labor Leadership., Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Preparing for a Career in Labor Leadership., Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
    By ILGWU Training Institute. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Union Health Center. Good Buys This Week., 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
  February 3-16, 1958
  - Item 1: Good Buys This Week., Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
    By Union Health Center. February 3-16, 1958. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. What Happens When the Top Becomes the Bottom, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: What Happens When the Top Becomes the Bottom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
- I.L.G.W.U. Workers University. Course Booklet., 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Workers University. Course Booklet., Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Item is in English; Yiddish.
- Kenosha Labor Newspaper. September 16, 1954. Pgs. 1-8., Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
  Newspaper. September 16, 1954; September 23, 1954. Brittle.
  - Item 1: Kenosha Labor Newspaper. September 16, 1954. Pgs. 1-8., Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Newspaper. September 16, 1954; September 23, 1954. Brittle. Item is in English.
- Mendelsund, Henoch. I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Trade Union Service, 1952-1953., Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
  Talk given by Henoch Mendelsund. November 1952. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: The ILGWU Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt, and Reefer Makers' Union of Greater New York, Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
    By Henoch Mendelsund. Training for Trade Union Service, 1952-1953. Talk given by Henoch Mendelsund. November 1952. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Mendelsund, Henoch. I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Trade Union Service, 1959., 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: The ILGWU Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt, and Reefer Makers' Union of Greater New York, Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
    By Henoch Mendelsund. Training for Trade Union Service, 1959. Talk given by Henoch Mendelsund.. Item is in English.
- National Consumers League. The Conference on the Breakdown of Industrial Standards., 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
  December 1932.
  - Item 1: The Conference on the Breakdown of Industrial Standards., Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
    December 1932. Item is in English.
- New Republic. Labor's Best Tool., 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
  Reprinted from The New Republic, January 30, 1935.
  - Item 1: Labor's Best Tool., Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
    Reprinted from The New Republic, January 30, 1935. Item is in English.
- Pell, Orlie. Jobs in Worker Education., 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
  Reprinted from Adult Education Journal, v.9:no.2 (1950:Apr.)
  - Item 1: Jobs in Worker Education., Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
    By Orlie Pell. Reprinted from Adult Education Journal, v.9:no.2 (1950:Apr.). Item is in English.
- Perlman, Selig. Labor in the New Deal Decade., 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Labor in the New Deal Decade., Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
    By Selig Perlman. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Pictorial Union Dictionary. An Illustrated Guide to Terms Used in the Labor Movement., 1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Pictorial Union Dictionary. An Illustrated Guide to Terms Used in the Labor Movement., Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Ross, William. Organizing Problems., 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Organizing Problems., Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
    By William Ross. Item is in English.
- Starr, Mark. Publications. [folder 1 of 2], Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Vocational Education and Unesco, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Viewpoint, May, 1946. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Training for Union Service, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. 3 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Garment Workers: "Welfare Unionism", Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Current History, July, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Education for Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: "Creeping Socialism" vs. Limping Capitalism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from The Kenosha Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor and the American Way, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Oxford Social Studies Pamphlets. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Basis of World Organization and Labor's Contribution to International Understanding, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Chapter 12 from Foundations of World Organization: A Political and Cultural Appraisal. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Struggles for Industrial Power, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Paper presented at the Conference on the Scientific Spirit and Democratic Faith. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Dubious Definitions, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Item 10: The Progress and Problems of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. From NUEA Manual: Volume I. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Constant Catfish., Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Adult Education For Everybody. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Labor Education in Britain Shows Change., Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from The Kenosha Labor, October, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Why Union Education? Aims, History, and Philosophy of the Educational Work of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from the Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, v.92:no.3 (1948). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Facts of Life In Our Schools, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By William E. Bohn. Reprinted from The New Leader, January 10, 1955. Reviews of Mark Starr's book Labor in America. 3 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: What the Citizen Should Know About Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Machinists Monthly Journal, May, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Let's Look at Workers' Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. In American Federationist, v.64:no.8 (1957:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Union Welfare Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. In Current History, June, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: In the Beginning: The Word, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from A.L.A. Bulletin, July-August, 1951. Item is in English.
- Starr, Mark. Publications. [folder 2 of 2], Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: The American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. Oxford Spectrum Series: Aspects of Contemporary Life. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workers Education in Britain: Can It Teach Us Any Lessons?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Labor Age. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Fight Against Militarism: How American and British Labor Can Cooperate., Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 4: Is N.Y. World Friend of Labor? Liberal Daily Blurs Issues, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 5: Can British Labor Teach Us? The British and American Scenes Compared, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 6: Next Steps By British Labor: New Problems and Tactics., Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 7: British Labor in Difficulties, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 8: New Parties and Prospects in The British Labor Scene, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 9: Lessons of the British Crisis, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 10: The British I.L.P. Remains Inside the Labor Party, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 11: Workers' Education on Wheels, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Concerning Workers' Education, v.1:no.6 (1934/35:Dec/Jan.) From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A Trade Union Pioneers in Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Railway Clerk, v.34:no.11 (1935:Nov.) From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Workers' Education: U.S. and Britain, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In The Workmen's Circle Call, v.8:no.1 (1940:Jan.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Workers Education in Great Britain and in America., Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Workers Age, March 2, 1940. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Consumer Education and Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Shall the New York Teachers' Union Charter Be Revoked?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr; Charles J. Hendley. Debate, March 14, 1941. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Labor and the Cooperative Movement As Allies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Economic Justice, v.10:no.2 (1941:Nov.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: American Labor and the Book, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Saturday Review, v.37:no.36 (1954:Sept. 4). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Education More Abundant, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Proceedings of the Centennial Symposium of the Continuing Education Service of Michigan State College, February 25-26, 1955. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: A Trade Union Pioneers in Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In American Federationist, January, 1936. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: A Course in Trade Union Training, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In American Federationist, June, 1936. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The ILGWU, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Journal of Adult Education, v.9:no.1 (1937:Jan.) From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: A Union Accepts Youth's Challenge, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Child Study, March, 1938.From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: The Eye Route: Visual Aids, Means and Agencies, for Workers' Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Item 25: Workers' Education in Overalls, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Journal of Adult Education, v.11:no.1 (1939:Jan.) From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Workers' Education in Overalls, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Labor Record, January 26, 1939. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Labor Leadership, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Teachers College Record, v.40:no.7 (1939:April). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Unions and Vocational Guidance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr. In Occupations, v.17:no.7 (1939:April). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Workers' Education in the United States, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
    By Mark Starr; Eleanor G. Corr. Reprinted from Monthly Labor Review, July, 1939. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
- Starr, Mark. Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.2, 1937-1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: What Labor Is Doing, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. In Making Consumer Education Effective, Bulletin no.2 (1940:July). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Consumer Education and Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Training for Union Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Workers' Education Today, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. L.I.D. Phamphlet Series. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Worker, His Union, and the Public Schools, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from The Lithographers Journal, March, 1942. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: New Europe and America, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)